All these things that can be changed like mirrors etc.
here I need documents,
which parts have been changed, let me
show you right now the mirror
of this scooter was also broken from the side
also so hello guys welcome back to my channel and
today we have in front of us X 125 and you
can see it has met with a small accident so I will
show you now that
if you want to take insurance claim then
what will be the process for that and how to do it,
see its glass etc. is also broken, the
rest of its rear light is broken so
they ask all these things also that friend
how did this happen, I mean someone has to tell us like this,
someone hit it from behind, so all these
parts have to be changed now, one this part is done, all this is done, so
now I will go to the showroom i.e.
its service center and
see it, all these things that can be changed,
mirrors etc. I will tell you
what you need for this and
how to get it done, how will it happen, so let's go
to the showroom now and you will get all the information,
you will watch the full video, so let's go  So,
we have reached the service center and
I will show you the documents that are required here, it is
RC, Aadhar card,
PAN card, driving license and
what is the story, in the story you have to tell
how your accident happened or did
someone hit you from behind or how did you
fall somewhere, whatever it is, you have to tell that, you
can see it, you can tell anything as per your understanding
and that is, the parts that are covered in it, the rest of it, the
vehicle number, etc., you have to write all these and give them,
you have to get the photocopies of all these things like driving license etc. done and give them, let us write it now and
make our story and see
what happens next, we have completed the formalities
and now we are leaving the final scooter,
our scooter is attached below, so
now they have written a lot of parts to be covered in it
here
but now the checkers who will come
from the insurance company will tell
which parts will be final changed, so let us
see, then now it takes 10-15 days, a week or two
weeks minimum, so
Now let's see how much it costs
and what all is involved, I will tell you
in the next video too, so hello guys, the
video that I was showing you right now, the
scooter has not arrived yet, it has been 10 days since
I was given the scooter, so whatever
I saw in it, I showed
you which parts have changed, I will show you, you
can see the front RH means
right panel and the inner
leg is the inner cover of the lug, so it means that
one of our panels has changed and
one of this panel has changed, the inner lug
guard, the rest of it, its
mirror was also broken, there was a
lot of break in it from the side of the scooter and the rear
light was also broken, so till now all these
things have not changed, they have changed only the front in such a way that
you will
feel that a lot has changed, so now let's
talk to them on this topic, the
total amount that we have to pay now, which they will
charge from us, so in that there was
some 147, you can see, so now we will talk to them
about such rear light  And when
we had told everything in the story that
someone had hit the scooter from behind and it fell on the right side, then
everything was clear, everything had to be
changed but they have not changed it, so let us
talk to them and then
see what happens next, so guys, it happens like this that
you can get as many parts written as you want
but the parts that have to be covered get covered very little,
so let us see now and then
talk.